The
lights
are bright But the room is cold Another story
that's bored and sold I'm trying to find a reason
why Beneath this plastic, empty sky
When the world is spinning out of my control
You're the one true thing that I can't hold
Through the static and the driving rain You're
the one who keeps me sane You are the shelter You
are the truth I ain't gonna shake this fool
They pull us under They push us high They build us
up just to watch us die It's hard to know who you
can trust When all the promises turn to dust
But when the world is spinning out of my control
You're the one true thing that I can hold Through
the static and the driving rain You're the one
who keeps me sane You are the shelter You are the
truth My anchor in this crazy you
Okay.
So let them talk, let them stare As long as you are
standing there I'm not afraid of what's to come I
know where I belong
Cause when the world is spinning out of my
control You're the one true thing that I can hold
Through the static and the driving rain You're
the one who keeps me sane You are the shelter You
are the truth My anchor in this crazy youth My
anchor My anchorhose
Mmm.